coursereport.com 2019-04-12

# Privacy Policy

Last Updated on May 24th, 2018.

CourseGuide Inc. ("us", "we", or "our") operates coursereport.com (the "Site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit our Site such as the collection and use of the personal information you provide. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, because by visiting or using this Site, you agree to its terms.

### Information that We Collect

Personal Information: Depending on the Services you are visiting or using, we may collect various types of information from and about you, including information that can personally identify you. This information includes, but is not limited to: name, age, zip code, email address, telephone number, demographic information, education and scholastic information (including but not limited to level of education, desired level of educational program, and areas of interest), current occupation, military status, governmental loan status, information about any transaction you conduct or submit to on or through the Services, and other information that would allow online or offline contact with you as an individual (collectively, “Personal Information”).

Non-Personal Information: We also collect Usage Information (as defined below) and other information from and about you that does not personally identify you or allow us or others to contact you individually online or offline ("Non-Personally Identifiable Information" or "Non-PII"). We may combine Non-PII with other information in a way that allows you to be identified or personally contacted. If this happens, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information.

How We Collect Information: We may collect information from you in the following ways:

* Information Provided by You. We collect information provided by you when you (1) inquire about or obtain our services or products; (2) communicate with us or request information about or from us, whether via email or other means; (3) fill out forms or fields on the Services; (4) register as a user or sign-up for any of our newsletters, materials or services through the Services; (5) create profiles; (6) provide reviews or participate in our online surveys or questionnaires; (8) input information into our interactive programming features or participate in our online forums; (9) participate in any of our marketing initiatives, including contests, scholarship offers, events, or promotions; and (10) post to the Services or provide user-generated content or submissions to us, including without limitation media files, photos, videos, documents or other information, and contributions to a chat room, list serve, blog, or other open forum or community feature that we make available on the Services ("User Contributions").

* Information from Other Sources. We may collect information about you from other services that we may provide, our affiliates, third-party or public sources (such as from public forums, social networks, and blogs), other users of the Services, and our business partners.

* Automatic Information Collection. We and our service providers use automatic data collection technologies to collect and store Usage Information (as defined below). This information helps us evaluate how our visitors use and navigate the Site on an aggregate basis, including but not limited to the number and frequency of visitors to each Site, and the length of their visits. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality. We also may allow third-party advertising companies and ad networks to use automatic data collection technologies to collect Usage Information for purposes of providing interest based ads. See the Automatic Information Collected Technologies and Usage Information and the Third-Party Advertisers and Interest-Based Ads sections for more information.

### How We Use the Information that We Collect

We may use your information, including Personal Information, to:

* Provide products and services requested by you;

* Provide customer support, including responding to your requests and questions and troubleshooting and resolving problems or complaints, and for any other purposes that we deem appropriate;

* Verify the information you provide to us;

* Communicate with you;

* Confirm your identity and eligibility to use the Services;

* Establish and manage your account, as applicable;

* Perform research and analysis to develop and improve the Services and other products and services that we may offer;

* Understand and anticipate your use of or interest in, our products, services, and content, and the products, services, and content offered by others;

* Develop and display products, services, and content tailored to your interests on the Services and other online properties;

* Measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, and programming, and other activities;

* Offer you personalized information and products, services, promotions, contests, or scholarships of ours, our affiliates, or our third-party business partners that may be of interest to you;

* Manage our business and operations;

* We use the information we automatically collect (such as contact information, IP address and basic browser and system details) to help us optimize our sites and the services we offer on the Site and may offer in the future;

* To provide you with a customized browsing experience;

* Protect the security and integrity of the Services;

* Carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use and any other applicable agreements and policies;

* Use or post User Contributions as permitted in our Terms of Use; and

* Fulfill any other purposes for which you provide your information and for any other purpose as described to you at the time your information is collected or for which your consent is given.

### Our Sharing Practices

We may disclose or share information from or about you, including your Personal Information, as follows:

* With our non-affiliated third-party business partners, service providers, and vendors to enable them to assist us in providing you the products or services you request through the Services or to provide us with support for our internal and business operations, such as customer service, data processing, data storage, research, analytics, web hosting, marketing, providing suggestions and strategies to improve our business processes and the services we provide, and delivery of promotional or transactional materials. We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your Personal Information only as necessary to provide these services to us. With other non-affiliated companies, parties, or organizations (with whom we maintain business relationships) when you engage in certain activities through the Services or services that are sponsored or provided by them, including, but not limited to requesting or purchasing products or services offered by these third parties, electing to receive information or communications from them, or electing to participate in contests, sweepstakes, games, scholarships, or other programs sponsored or provided by these third parties, in whole or in part. For example, if you provide us with Personal Information for the purposes of being matched with an educational institution, we share your information with the educational institutions with whom you are matched so that they may contact you regarding educational or related opportunities. When we disclose your information to these third parties, your information will become subject to the information use and sharing practices of these third parties, and these third parties will not be restricted by this Privacy Policy with respect to their use and further sharing of your information.

* If you submit information to an advertiser or other third party that is made available on or through Course Report, the information obtained during your visit to that advertiser’s website, and the information you give to the advertiser will be governed by the advertiser’s privacy policy. For further information on such advertiser’s use of your information, please visit the applicable privacy policy of such advertisers. Advertisers made available on this site have separate policy practices for which Course Report has no responsibility or liability.

* In addition, from time to time, we may share Personal Information (such as e-mail addresses and other contact information such as name, email address and phone number) with selected third parties, so they may offer educational or non-educational goods and services that we believe may be of interest to our customers.

* We may disclose information we collect from or about you when we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law; when we believe that disclosure is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or other similar legal process served on our Site; to enforce or apply applicable terms and conditions and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our company, our affiliates, our other customers or users of the Services, or others. If some or all of our business assets are sold or transferred, whether through a sale, acquisition, merger, consolidation, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other corporate change involving us and/or our affiliates, we may transfer the corresponding information regarding our customers and users of the Services, including Personal Information, to third parties evaluating or facilitating the transaction. We also may retain a copy of such information. Nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to interfere with our ability to transfer all or part of our business, equity interests, or assets (including the Services) to an affiliate or non-affiliated third party at any time, for any purpose, without any limitation, and without notice or any compensation to you, whatsoever.

* We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other Personal Information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they unlawfully collect from the Site. We will try to protect your privacy, however, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your Personal Information or private communications will always remain private.

### Automatic Information Collection Technologies and Usage Information

We and our service providers automatically collect "Usage Information" from or about you, such as information about your computer or mobile device, IP address, web browser, computer or device platform, related software and settings you are using, browsing actions and patterns, the referring page that linked you to us and the website you visit after using the Services, and other usage activity on the Services. Collection of Usage Information helps us to improve the Services and to deliver a better and more personalized service by enabling us to, among other things: (1) estimate our audience size and usage patterns; (2) store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize the Services according to your individual interests; (3) speed up your searches; and (4) recognize you when you return to the Services.

We and certain third parties, such as but not limited to advertising service providers, may use certain technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across different services.

The automatic collection technologies we may use for this automatic information collection include cookies, browser cookies, session cookies, persistent cookies, and web beacons. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

For more information about managing your privacy settings regarding automatic collection of Usage Information, see the Your Choices about How We Use and Disclose Your Information section.

### Third-Party Advertisers and Interest-Based Ads

We may permit third-party advertising companies or ad networks to display third-party advertisements on our websites and/or automatically collect Usage Information from our websites for purposes of determining your preferences and delivering interest-based advertising and content to you on the Services or other online properties, including those operated by third parties. Those ads may include ads for our products or services or for other companies' products or services.

These third-party advertisers may combine the Usage Information with Personal Information you directly submit to them or that they receive from other sources, or the Usage Information they collect may include information that could allow someone to specifically contact you online without necessarily knowing your identity. We do not have access to or control over the automatic collection technologies that these third-party advertisers may use, and the information practices of these third-party advertisers are subject to these parties' respective privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy.

If you click on a link to a third party site, including on an advertisement, you will leave the Site you are visiting and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personally identifiable information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as this Site. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party website that is linked to this Site, you should read that site’s privacy statement before providing any personally identifiable information.

### Third-Party Content

The Services and all electronic communications sent in connection with the Services, may contain links, videos, images, or other content provided by third parties. We do not necessarily endorse these websites, products, services, or practices. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the privacy and security practices of these third parties. We recommend that you review the privacy and security policies of these third parties to determine how they handle information they may collect from or about you once you are on the third party site.

### Your Choices About Use and Disclosure of Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the Personal Information you provide to us. Below are some mechanisms that provide you with control over your information:

* Promotional Emails or other Electronic Communications. If you do not wish to receive promotional emails or other electronic communications from us, including but not limited to our e-newsletters, contact us at hello@coursereport.com to opt-out or follow the unsubscribe process at the bottom of the promotional email or other electronic communication. Note that even if you opt-out, you may still receive transactional or account-related emails from us (e.g., emails related to the completion of your registration, correction of user data, password reset requests, reminder emails that you have requested, and any other similar communications essential to your transactions on or made through the Services).

* Automatic Information Collection Technologies and Advertising. The "help" function of your browser should contain instructions on how to set your browser to not accept new cookies, to notify you when a cookie is issued, or how to disable cookies altogether. If Flash cookies are used on the Services, you can manage your Flash cookie settings, by visiting the Flash player settings page on Adobe's website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of the Services may be inaccessible or not function properly.

### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Accessing and Correcting Your Information

You may have the ability to view or edit some of your information online, by logging into [https://www.coursereport.com](https://www.coursereport.com/) and visiting your account profile page. 

We cannot delete your Personal Information except by also deleting your user account, if applicable. Once your user account is deleted, it cannot be recovered. We also may not accommodate a request to change or delete information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirements, not allow us to enforce our agreements, be contrary to our Terms of Use or any other applicable agreement between you and us, or cause the information to be incorrect. After deletion of your user account, your Personal Information may remain on our archived database and records. If you delete or request the deletion of your User Contributions from the Services, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied, stored, or reposted to another website by other users of the Services.

Any updates you make or request to be made to your Personal Information will be applied in our own records but will not be updated in the records of the educational institutions or other third parties to which we have already shared your information. If you would like to make updates to the information that has been shared with educational institutions and other third parties, you will need to contact them separately.

### Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.

Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

### Do Not Track

We support the Do Not Track browser setting. Do Not Track (or DNT) is a preference you can set in your browser to let the websites you visit know that you do not want them collecting certain information about you.

For more details about Do Not Track, including how to enable or disable this preference, visit http://termsfeed.com/do-not-track

### The Services Are Not for Children

The Services are not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child younger than 13 years old, we will endeavor to delete that information and terminate the child's account (if any).

### International Users

The Site was created by and is controlled, operated and administered by Course Guide, Inc within the United States of America utilizing servers located in the United States of America. We make no representation that materials at this Site are appropriate or available for transmission to or from, or use in, locations outside of the jurisdiction(s) stated above and accessing any Site from any jurisdiction where such Site’s contents are illegal is prohibited. You may not use the Site or export the materials in violation of import or export laws and regulations. If you access a Site from a location outside of the United States, you are responsible for compliance with all local laws. If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the personal data you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. Whenever you submit any personal data to us, you consent to this transfer.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. This Privacy Policy will reflect the date it was last updated or amended. If we make any material amendments, we will notify you by posting a notice of the updated or amended Privacy Policy on the Services. All amendments will take effect immediately upon our posting of the updated Privacy Policy on the Services. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by additional means, such as posting a notice on the homepage of the Services or sending you an email. Please check this Privacy Policy each time you use the Services to ensure you are aware of any changes in our practices. Your continued use of the Services will indicate your acceptance of the changes to the Privacy Policy.

Last Updated on May 24th, 2018. This Privacy Policy is effective immediately for all users.
